Sushma_HR: Good afternoon, everyone. Welcome to Project Management Interviews. I'm Sushma Hetal Tamisha Foundation, Woman FOG
Sushma_HR: Your first round will be the group discussion, and in this group discussion, you're going to discuss about your understanding of Apogee.
Sushma_HR: And what's your understanding about the project management in general at Homesha Foundation?
Sushma_HR: So, I'm giving you 5 minutes time. If you want, you can recall, you can note down the points, you can,
Sushma_HR: start your discussion. So, just give us 5 minutes, we will get back to you.
Sushma_HR: Meanwhile, you can also… Get ready with your points, what to discuss.
Haniah Fatima: Could you tell the topic again, please, if that is okay?
Sushma_HR: your understanding about A4G?
Sushma_HR: Like, about Omisha Foundation, Huang and I4G? Primarily, your understanding?
Sushma_HR: About Apogee?
Sushma_HR: And what's your understanding about project management in general at Tamasha Foundation?
Sushma_HR: So, we clearly mentioned everything in the job description.
Sushma_HR: So you can see a lengthy job description about mentioning about Gong, A4G, and the role and responsibilities of the role of the project management intern role.
Sushma_HR: If you want to reconfirm the things, you can work with the JD.
Sushma_HR: Again, and come up with the points, what do you understand?
Sushma_HR: So, Shivansh and Sandy, I'm ascending the room, please join in that room.
Sushma_HR: Guys, I'm giving you 5 minutes time.
Sushma_HR: Meanwhile, like, let us discuss in the breakout room.
Sushma_HR: And we will be back within 5 minutes. Meanwhile, you can also… Get ready with the points.
Sushma_HR: Am I clear? Everyone, like, any, like…
Sushma_HR: Anything that you would like to, have any further confirmations? Am I clear with the topics what you're going to discuss in the group discussion?
Sushma_HR: After 5 minutes?
Sushma_HR: I'm repeating again.
Sushma_HR: Your understanding about A4G? About company?
Sushma_HR: And the role. Project management intern role.
Sushma_HR: Okay.
Sushma_HR: Hold on 5 minutes.
Sushma_HR: Hello!
Sushma_HR: Hello, guys. Are you ready?
Sushma_HR: Who will be going to discuss? See, guys, it's a group discussion, no need to ask permissions in between, can I speak, can I say? But…
Sushma_HR: My request is, if one person is completely sharing their point, after that, you please start and share your… like, you know, agreeing with them, or sharing your understanding like that.
Sushma_HR: Pragati, could you please turn on your video?
Sushma_HR: Okay, so… yeah, ready? 1, 2, 3, start, go ahead.
Haniah Fatima: If it's okay, should I start, if it's something? Like you mentioned, the topic was, what is A4G, what is Wong, and then what is my role as a project… product intern here?
Sushma_HR: For interacting, first of all, let's discuss only about effort. Then later we can, you know…
Sushma_HR: have another first let let us discuss about airport your understanding about airport.
Haniah Fatima: Okay, so about A4G, what is it, as the name suggests, AI for good, is that what I believe is that, nowadays, everything is based on AI. Whatever we do, there is some… we do use some kind of AI, and sometimes what we realize is that we do not use it as sustainably or as
Haniah Fatima: authenticity as possible. So there are privacy reasons we might. There might be bias. There might be some other security concerns as well. So what I think a 4G provides is making use of AI in a sustainable way. That is what I heard.
Haniah Fatima: And that there are three major topics which I have seen when I was going through it. That is sustainability.
Haniah Fatima: Then an AI for governance, and then mental well-being also, which I have seen, and
Haniah Fatima: what I found is that, first one about AI governance, is that when I was… as I… I'm a computer science graduate, and I did AI as a part, and then it was… it showed me that AI governance is that whenever we use AI, it is majorly based on the amount of the data you get.
Haniah Fatima: So there is a chance of bias as well and sometimes.
Haniah Fatima: People collect information more than required. So sometimes it is important that there is something which governs and makes sure that we are using.
Rishav Kumar: Yes.
Haniah Fatima: AI in a responsible and a sustainable way.
Haniah Fatima: If anybody would like to continue.
Vidushi Sinha: Yeah, so, like, my views in this, like, for this Umesha Foundation, like, A4G is not just, using AI for productivity.
Vidushi Sinha: I think, but it is also using AI as a tool to improve human… human well-being, rather, like, for using just… just like Hania said, like, for sustainability and all. So, like, most of the…
Vidushi Sinha: people see AIs as a tool for, like, productivity increase for their company, like, generating revenues and all.
Vidushi Sinha: so majorly focus on that. But this is, like, from this foundation, I thought that it is mainly used for the, like, how can we collaborate AI and generating well-beingness of human beings, rather than generating productivity and all.
Haniah Fatima: Okay.
Chikamnene Vivian: Okay, once I…
Yashika: Okay.
Yashika: So A4G, like, they said, like, AI for good. It definitely is helpful, like, especially, I feel like, we are leveraging AI in, like, every field currently. So what, I liked about is, like, it is focusing, currently on the sustainability, socioeconomic issues.
Yashika: And also on mental well-being. We have not, like, heard, like, generally about it, too much about it.
Yashika: So currently, everybody is using AI for like website development or on technical issues. So it will definitely give like good solutions. If we leverage AI in like sustainability and like well-being, well-being for mental well-being solutions.
Chikamnene Vivian: Okay, for me, what time?
Chikamnene Vivian: What I understand by AI for good.
Chikamnene Vivian: for it's based on using AI for the right purposes. A lot of people use AI for the wrong for the wrong reason. So like the name implies AI for good and filling the Google form. I found out that the organizations like their so aim is for governance and mental health and social impact. So it's basically using AI for these 3 things. I'm not using it for
Chikamnene Vivian: a harmful source for a harmful reason. So many people use AI to boycott so many things, thereby making them lazy, and they can't be productive again. It's simply to use AI for sustainability and productivity.
Chikamnene Vivian: Thank you.
Sujal Yadav: Okay, so, based on my… based on the overviews you shared about A4G Global.
Sujal Yadav: Cooperative AI for Good appeared to be a mission-driven collaborative initiative rather than a traditional software company. It focuses on connecting expert organizations and policymakers to the advanced responsible users.
Sujal Yadav: Of AI for the interview, understanding the idea behind the work likely to more value, valuable than memorizing facts. So what A4G global.
Sujal Yadav: So, basically, so it is the platform that AI researchers, universities, government, and policy makers Ensure to have goal.
Sujal Yadav: And unlike other companies, they sell AI product. A4G appear on the focus on research, collaboration, policy, discourse, educational initiatives. So as I have researched about the vision of A4G, it to create the future where artificial intelligence improve people life while remaining transparent, exclusive, and sustainable.
Sujal Yadav: The main AI should… To improve society, respect human rights, protect privacy.
Sujal Yadav: let's come upon the mission. Their mission can be broke into 4 pillars, AI for sustainability.
Sujal Yadav: AI for mental health, AI for responsible AI governance, And collaboration.
Sujal Yadav: And what kind of work might A4G do? In my research, I found that AI
Sujal Yadav: About the A4G, that research projects, workshops, hackathons, etc. And why should you hire me as a product management intern? So…
Sujal Yadav: Eventually, I'm an excellent AI researcher who needs a project manager to keep initiative organized. A project manager in terms of skills, I have a good in coordinations, meeting track, timelines, managed documents, follow-ups with stakeholders.
Shivaansh: Sujal, sorry to cut you off.
Sushma_HR: Just please hold on,
Shivaansh: For this round, we would want you to just discuss about your knowledge about A4G and what you understand about what we do over here.
Sujal Yadav: Oh, sorry by myself.
Shivaansh: No worries. So guys, in this round, we just want you guys to discuss about A4G and what you guys think we do over here. What A4G is about.
Shivaansh: Alright.
Sujal Yadav: Okay, sir.
Shivaansh: All right.
Sujal Yadav: That's all from my side, guys. Thank you.
Haniah Fatima: The one thing which I noticed was sustainable use as well. Just to give a basic example, for example, if you go to a building and then you see, you have to come up with ways, for example, if AI can find ways on how to reduce the usage of electricity, that is a way of sustainable use.
Haniah Fatima: But here in Air Fuji, it's also about finding ways where we can reduce…
Haniah Fatima: a more amount of work in a way so that it's reduced in a and we can use it in a more sustainable and less.
Haniah Fatima: Right.
Haniah Fatima: That is what I saw.
Sujal Yadav: But as I've seen, the high usage of AI causes a lot of water.
Sujal Yadav: From a recent survey of OpenAI, AI takes more water
Sujal Yadav: For the research and for the critical thinking so it might in future.
Sujal Yadav: get some sort of water shortage due to AI, so I guess using AI in a sustainable manner is a good thing, rather than overusing and implementing it on every small task which can easily handle by humans, rather than fully depending on AI.
Sujal Yadav: From my…
Sushma_HR: Pragati, you are not audible, check your audio connectivity.
Sushma_HR: Anyone would like to add anything about A4G?
Haniah Fatima: I think one way we can conclude it, for example, is by saying that instead of just building technology just because we can make it, I think A4G tries to find a real world problem and then tries to find a solution for it. I think that is what A4G does in a short way.
Sushma_HR: Come again, the point you just shared.
Haniah Fatima: My…
Rishav Kumar: Money.
Haniah Fatima: But that instead of just building technology just because it is possible, A4G starts with finding the real world problem and tries to find a solution for it in the ways which we have mentioned.
Haniah Fatima: that is sustainable, that covers the AI governance part, as well as the mental well-being of the people around, the stakeholders, the young students, the people who are working in the industries.
Haniah Fatima: Like that.
Sujal Yadav: I would like to add something on it.
Sujal Yadav: So…
Sujal Yadav: So, A4G is a tech, A4G because it's combined the technology with a meaningful social impact, rather than focusing on building AI systems.
Sujal Yadav: And it also work in the favor of, Give it to the community.
Sujal Yadav: Rather than just making AI and implementing it everywhere.
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, that's all from my side.
Yashika: I also want to add one thing. As, Sujalwan, mentioned about, like, a lot of, usage of water is being used in data centers for AI. So, A4G is also focusing, like, instead of, blindly following the AI trend and, using it, like, everywhere.
Yashika: we, like, it is focusing majorly, like, how and how, like, sustain… in, how, like, a good sustainable way we can find solutions for problems that, like, if… like, we just need it, actually, instead of, like, blindly following.
Sushma_HR: of…
Rishav Kumar: Nope.
Sushma_HR: Guys, so… Do you have any… yeah, anyone would like to add?
Rishav Kumar: I'm, for the combined technology with, meaningful social impact, instead of just building AI, AI system and, pushing them everywhere, and the focus on what actually the community technology serve, with the purpose, and, not the other way around.
Rishav Kumar: And, what I, what I really like about A4G is that They… they don't wear…
Rishav Kumar: They don't start with technology, they start with a real problem in, in a community. And, they ask how AI solve, this problem responsibly, responsibly.
Rishav Kumar: And, so instead of just building an advanced AI system, and then trying to find a phased
Rishav Kumar: Then find to… Find a place to them.
Rishav Kumar: And they start doing, the opposite, and, they are saying, the sustainability.
Sushma_HR: See, okay. So most of you, what I got to know and hear, that a few of your understanding is, some of your assumptions. I will clarify that, but, before going to that.
Sushma_HR: anyone would like to add?
Sushma_HR: About Wong.
Sushma_HR: Because it is also mentioned in the job description. Currently, we are not currently, we are not much active in that, but just for understanding.
Haniah Fatima: I saw a post on your LinkedIn as well regarding an essay competition which is going to be held. Is that under Wong as well?
Sushma_HR: It's under A4G.
Sushma_HR: Okay. It's APOG Intellects Essex Contest, AI Work and Society.
Haniah Fatima: Okay, I see.
Haniah Fatima: But I believe that Wong, what I have seen and what I've came across is that Wong is providing you a platform where different people with different backgrounds, for example, students or people who are working in companies or somebody, they have a place, they have a platform where they can share their ideas about and people from different backgrounds, they can collaborate and come up.
Sushma_HR: Alright, see, okay, I don't want to waste much time. Now let's discuss about,
Sushma_HR: Like, project management in general, or would you understand by seeing the job description of roles and responsibilities?
Sushma_HR: Just share your understanding, discuss that, and again, I would like to add on that, please don't assume, basic project manager, something like that. So, whatever mentioned in the job description, just, you know, share your understanding.
Vidushi Sinha: So, like, my understanding of this role is, like, basically to ensure that, like, social impact initiative, like, moving from ideas to successful execution.
Vidushi Sinha: It involves… basically involves, like, planning projects, managing timelines, like, coordinating resources, and anticipating risk, like, majorly risk management also, and resolving the issue, like, what… what all the risk…
Vidushi Sinha: can be happened, so we have to, like, provide, resolutions also, and maintaining quality throughout the project lifecycle. So this… this is the basic understanding I have about this role.
Pragati Sharma: My understanding of project management is that it's a process of planning, organizing, executing, monitoring, and successfully delivering the deliverables. So, like, the main part of being a project… in a project management team is that to ensure that you, like.
Pragati Sharma: Engage the stakeholders properly, and ensure that the quality is
Pragati Sharma: always on the first priority, and we, like, deliver the deliverables on the time. That's what, like, basic understandings I have, and, like, managing the team properly, and ensuring that
Pragati Sharma: You are providing the right resources and ensuring and monitoring their performance and about the quality and.
Pragati Sharma: Timelines and all, that's all.
Vidushi Sinha: Like, one more point I want to add, like, basically, what this role, except, like, it's not a traditional coordination role, like, don't want to, like, just coordinate two meetings and all, like, we have to get the ownership role also, like, we have to take the fully ownership of this waterway planning, and the…
Vidushi Sinha: And what are we are, like, organization views and that. So, like, we have to translating the organization vision into, like, a structured execution plans.
Chikamnene Vivian: Okay, what I understand by project management intention. Project management is all about planning.
Chikamnene Vivian: and the planning and execution of a particular project.
Chikamnene Vivian: This involves coordination, that the deliverables are met and on time. So for this, this is a non-IT role, like it's a non-IT part of project management, and it typically revolves around coordination. So this is ensuring that stakeholders, there are no disagreements between stakeholders, and timelines are met within limits, and deliverables are
Chikamnene Vivian: Are met in order to achieve a particular goal.
Sujal Yadav: Okay. From, my understanding, the project management intern role at A4G is about supporting AI for good initiatives by helping plan projects, coordinate with different stakeholders, track timelines, maintain documentation, and ensure smooth communication across the team. Since A4G works with researchers, policymakers, and industry leaders on the area like sustainability, mental health, and responsible AI.
Sujal Yadav: Governance effect effective projects coordination is essential in my I believe my organizational skills.
Sujal Yadav: Willing to learn and… learn and ability to communicate clearly would allow me to contribute to the… this initiative while growing as a project management professional.
Sushma_HR: Guys.
Sushma_HR: See, don't, like, don't share simply that, you know, planning to execution the steps.
Sushma_HR: I just want to hear, in the job description we mentioned clearly about the core responsibility areas.
Sushma_HR: Can you please start discussing about those core responsibility areas?
Yashika: Based on the job description. At 1st the core responsibility 1st was the end to end planning like making sure like what the vision is, and building a proper roadmap according to it, prioritizing what the solutions need to be prioritized.
Yashika: And, making sure… making the timelines, how it will be done, when it will be done, and, making a proper plan out of it. Second was… was, risk management,
Yashika: prevent… preventing, preventing and making solutions, at first, like, if there are short… resource shortages.
Yashika: or some, timeline delays, making sure that that is proper. Third one was, issue management. That is, like, a continuous process, making sure, like, if it is everything, going properly. If there are any issues, then, like.
Yashika: Solving those issues, on time, so that the deliverables are not, like.
Yashika: like at risk. 3rd was quality assurance like proper and quality solutions are being delivered. And And.
Yashika: Yeah, that's it.
Sushma_HR: Perfect! Very good.
Sushma_HR: Guys, anyone would like to add?
Sushma_HR: just talk about the response… focus responsibility areas. I… I just… I don't want to generalize answers or assume answers.
Sushma_HR: So, whatever we mentioned, by saying that, what do you understand? Just share that.
Vidushi Sinha: So, though, by defining point by point, like, I can say, like, first, which is the end-to-end planning execution, which is, like, leadership.
Vidushi Sinha: So, this concept really convert the project vision into a clear execution plan. Then, second part is, like, future risk management, like, which identify problems before they happen.
Vidushi Sinha: And, like, predicting possible delays and identify resources, shortages, this… this all comes under this.
Vidushi Sinha: And the third is, like, issue management, like, whatever risk we have analyzed, we have to solve that also, like, solve problem that has already occurred also in the past.
Vidushi Sinha: And what can, like, what can occur in future also, so we have to solve that, like, identify issues quickly, categorize them by severity, like, owning ownership, assigning ownership to different people, like, who comes under this.
Vidushi Sinha: And, like, fourth is, like, quality assurance. Like, ensure work meets the accepted standards, like, define quality benchmarks, review deliveries.
Vidushi Sinha: And check documentation, if available, and… and to prepare also documentation if something… something is gapping, like, between two parties.
Vidushi Sinha: And, like, final… maybe resource mobilization and alignment. Like, ensure that project has the right people and resources available. So these are my understanding about the JDs.
Chikamnene Vivian: Okay, to add to what she said, and based on the rule, based on the rule description, is basically to
Chikamnene Vivian: to make sure that end-to-end planning are done. And another one is weeks management, making sure that weeks are avoided or future weeks are seen before then. Then another one is resource mobilization, making sure that resources needed for a particular task, they are all available and if not available, a clear communication in between them.
Chikamnene Vivian: So, that's it. Then, oh, that was, quality assurance and the rest of them. But for the road, the, the, the main,
Chikamnene Vivian: The main job for the interns are just end-to-end planning, quality assurance, resource mobilization, risk management, etc.
Sushma_HR: Honey, honey, what happened to your laptop?
Sushma_HR: Like, are you facing any bandwidth issues?
Haniah fatim: I'm so sorry, some, the network got cut, so I had to come back again, so I hope that is okay, so I rejoined again.
Sushma_HR: Okay, I'm going to just rejoin from your laptop.
Sushma_HR: Actually…
Haniah fatim: I… it's a little bit difficult right now, because I unfortunately couldn't carry my charger, and I'm out of station, so unfortunately the battery went off, so… Is it okay if I do it on my phone for a while?
Sushma_HR: Can you please, rotate your mobile into landscape?
Haniah fatim: Is this fine?
Sushma_HR: No, no, check that, check the correct direction.
Sushma_HR: Okay.
Sushma_HR: It's in reverse, yeah, alright.
Haniah fatim: I hope this is okay.
Sushma_HR: Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's okay.
Sushma_HR: Guys, anyone would like to add?
Sujal Yadav: Oh, yeah.
Sushma_HR: Focus.
Sujal Yadav: I would like.
Sushma_HR: Responsible areas, yeah, please.
Sujal Yadav: Okay, so applying other focus areas, maintaining structural issues management to track, accelerate and resolve institutions.
Sujal Yadav: Spotting risks and early preventing delays and issues. Checking that the work being delivered meets expected quality. Helping ensure the right people and right resources available when needed.
Haniah fatim: I think everybody have basically covered all the points, but I would like to add in a fact
Haniah fatim: that, basically, what is risk management, and what is, crisis management, and what is prevention. Basically, prevent… risk management is something which is done before any casualty or any problem has occurred. So, it is about the steps which are taken
Haniah fatim: I'm sorry?
Haniah fatim: Can I speak?
Sushma_HR: Yeah, yeah, please go ahead.
Haniah fatim: Sure. So risk management is all about finding all the loopholes and finding out all the prob- there are two ways, impact and, the cause of occurrence. So if what is high, we have to see and we have to identify where there's a chance of it occurring a lot, and then we have to take up various measures in order to reduce that.
Haniah fatim: And what is, risk… what will happen is… so, in case any…
Haniah fatim: kind of casualty happens. So, that is the steps which are taken in order to minimize or reduce the impact.
Haniah fatim: So that is one other thing which we have to focus on. Another one is quality, which people have been mentioning.
Haniah fatim: I think it is about providing… it's not always about the quantity, like we said, it's also about providing the right amount, the correct amount of information, the right amount of whatever is required. So quality is also a big importance, and following timelines.
Haniah fatim: That's all.
Sushma_HR: Alright. Okay.
Sushma_HR: Lastly, whoever didn't get any time to speak now.
Sushma_HR: You can speak.
Sushma_HR: I'm giving the time.
Sushma_HR: The garnet who didn't speak at all, you please take initiative and share your understanding.
Sushma_HR: Done. Rishi or Kumar, do you want to speak anything?
Rishav Kumar: No.
Sushma_HR: Alright. Okay.
Sushma_HR: So, let me, give a brief summary about A4G, WOM, and the project management in general.
Sushma_HR: So, firstly, let me discuss about the Gong. So, Omesha Foundation is having the two initiatives. The first one is Gong, Voice of New Generation.
Sushma_HR: And second initiative is A4G.
Sushma_HR: If a good impact, collaborate.
Sushma_HR: So, if I talk about the…
Sushma_HR: Hey, Wong. Voice of New Generation.
Sushma_HR: So… As Hanya said that, ma'am.
Sushma_HR: We are providing a platform to 12 to 18 age group of school-going students to raise their voices towards sustainability challenges.
Sushma_HR: And, like, so far, we organized 7 Sustana Spark events.
Sushma_HR: And providing them a platform to raise their voices.
Sushma_HR: And we increase them, motivate them to all to 18S group students. What are the innovative solutions that come up towards the sustainability challenges? Increasing them, motivating them to implement in their locality.
Sushma_HR: And we increase, motivate them through gamification.
Sushma_HR: So, usually their focus is towards the SDG goals.
Sushma_HR: This is about, a brief summary of Wonk.
Sushma_HR: Currently we are not, actively doing the events.
Sushma_HR: But in future, we will be going to be, rework on that.
Rishav Kumar: Okay.
Sushma_HR: Current Omisha Foundation is focusing mainly In FOG.
Sushma_HR: Air Force Impact Collaborative. The name itself suggests A4G means air for good.
Sushma_HR: So we would like to… Collaborate, with, policy makers, researchers.
Sushma_HR: global leaders who are working towards Air For Good.
Sushma_HR: So, we would like to collaborate with them.
Sushma_HR: And we want to, like, you know, have…
Sushma_HR: impact the AI-driven changes by bringing all together of these experts who are from these focus areas. AI governance, AI for mental well-being, and AI for socio-economic sustainability. So, AI4G is having these three focus areas. So, if I talk about the mission.
Sushma_HR: The mission is about, like, you know, we would like to, collaborate, like, we would like to support the individuals and communities also, like, and also we would like to collaborate, with institutions, donors, policy makers.
Sushma_HR: global leaders, or we would like to collaborate for good impact. I'm bringing all together
Sushma_HR: just to create a, human-centered solutions for these three focus areas. This is over.
Sushma_HR: mission.
Sushma_HR: And if I talk about the vision, so our vision is something we, we, like, we believe that, something that, AI should be a natural extension of human goodness.
Sushma_HR: So, it should not be human harness, like most of people, like, you know, using the AI in a wrong way.
Sushma_HR: So, but we would like to, our vision is something that, like, where the world, which, where we can see the AI become, will be the natural extension.
Sushma_HR: And which can be enhanced the compassion, equity, like, you know, and well-being.
Sushma_HR: Not biased. So that, the AI shouldn't replace the human values. We are focusing… our vision is like that. The AI shouldn't replace the human values, and it should be, a natural extension of human goodness.
Sushma_HR: This is our vision.
Sushma_HR: And focusing, coming to the focus areas of these three focus areas, coming to the AI governance. So this is currently, it's our primary focus thing, which in AI governance, we are promoting the ethical and inclusive and transparent AI developments.
Sushma_HR: and exploring the AIS Faraj models that combine civilization, wisdom, and modern global policy frameworks.
Sushma_HR: And we would like to collaborate, like in these, like, you know, we are collaborating with the policymakers and coming up with the ethical policymaking and giving to the government, demanding or suggesting the government to implement those ethical policymaking through AIM.
Sushma_HR: And so that we can, you know.
Sushma_HR: We can overcome the bias stuff.
Sushma_HR: unfair decisions. So that, increasing… so in this, we are increasing the participatory governance, where, diverse stakeholders can help, like, you know, diverse stakeholders help and shape the AI policies.
Sushma_HR: So, this is our primary focus towards the AI governance, and coming to the AI for mental well-being.
Sushma_HR: We are supporting the professionals, which are affected by AI automations, so that, you know, in future, maybe they may lose of jobs.
Sushma_HR: Because of AI automation tools, etc. So, we just want to, like, you know, help the professionals who…
Sushma_HR: like, who is affected by the automation, so that in rediscovering… we are rediscovering their strengths and purpose. So, we are providing a platform, a tool for them, so that they can also have their own, explore in the AI, and they can be also start their own
Sushma_HR: solar entrepreneurships.
Sushma_HR: With the help of AI, so whoever going to lose their job, so they can also survive with their own, new skills with the help of AI tool. So all these three focus areas we are trying to, like, we are focusing to build the, AI, so that we can co-create the solu- solutions, with, these three focus areas.
Sushma_HR: And also… In this, A for mental well-being, we are promoting the…
Sushma_HR: reflection, self-awareness, and, intentional living. And also, we are using the AI, which to enhance, the human potential and well-being. It's not just for productivity. So, this is, about AI for mental well-being, and it is coming to the
Sushma_HR: AI social economic sustainability. So, in this, we are empowering the individuals to become AI-enabled solopreneurs and independent value creators.
Sushma_HR: And also, we are building a community which is repeated, and trust, systems.
Sushma_HR: and we increased the, deep expertise and long-term, values, which created the short-term market demand. So, like, in overall, like, A4G is, like, you know, to ensure that
Sushma_HR: AI serves the humanity.
Sushma_HR: by promoting the responsible, governance, human, you know, human, well-being, mental well-being, and also sustainable efforts. So, these are our focus for, this, FOG.
Sushma_HR: And currently, we are having the, contest, which is A4G Intellects Essay Contest, A4…
Sushma_HR: I work in society. So, as a project manager.
Sushma_HR: your project. So, we clearly mentioned that
Sushma_HR: The project management at Omisha will be non-IT project management. It's not IT project management.
Sushma_HR: So, our focus in the project management is event… as of now, we are focusing event-based project management. So, you will be given event as a project manage… as a project, you know? And you need to manage that project.
Sushma_HR: And currently, as a project manager, you will be responsible of managing the A4G IntellX essay contest. So, already, the project manager's, plan… sorry, already the project manager's,
Sushma_HR: planned, like, they are in the execution stage, but I would like to say that our project management is not only into, like, you know, focusing, coordinating, planning, execution, all those things. It's mainly focusing into
Sushma_HR: three KRIs, which is risk management and issue management. So, what are the processes or structures that you design in the project management, or the currently that we are following, in that
Sushma_HR: The project manager will be responsible for anticipating the future risk.
Sushma_HR: And, coming up with a mitigation plan.
Sushma_HR: So that, in future, we can avoid the risk.
Sushma_HR: And the issue management… the issue management, risk management will be ongoing, continuous process. And the issue management is mostly focusing into the current going issues.
Sushma_HR: What are the current going issues? You need to, analyze that, what's the root cause, what's the blocker, and come up with the resolution plan.
Sushma_HR: These are the major important thing that the project manager is expected, here.
Sushma_HR: And later, like, quality assurance, resource mobilization, you know that, so what are the quality
Sushma_HR: What are the deliverables that, like, you know, the team is delivering to you?
Sushma_HR: It is not about… so most of people, like, you know, assuming the project management is something that I have to be… make ensure that… to do the things. No, you are not ensured to do the… or completion the things, or delivering the things. The team will be going to do. You're going to organize and manage and track the things. So you need to…
Sushma_HR: Build the systems and structures, how to track the progress, how to get the… set the timelines, set the milestones, ensuring the risk and…
Sushma_HR: issues.
Sushma_HR: So coming to the quality assurance, you should have to define what are the quality benchmarks, and you need to review the deliverables from the… from your team, and make ensure that the quality should be up to the mark by analyzing based on your common sensical thinking.
Sushma_HR: This is the basic thing we are expecting from the project managers. And next, resource mobilization. So, what are the resources, or, do you identify that there are lack of resources to complete that, work in the respective teams, or, you know, any, any lack, or, like, you need to understand the…
Sushma_HR: Team members' competence, and you need to, you know, you assign the milestones, and also you need to
Sushma_HR: Also, ensure that, whether it's… everything is up to the mark, and if it is lagging anything, you need to ensure that, for providing the resources, or by communicating with HRs, or communicating with the organization, like that.
Sushma_HR: So, identifying the gaps and making sure that, you know.
Sushma_HR: Everything is to be on time, and the resources who are, like, you know, for each phase to complete the work by the team members, ensuring that everything resources are providing on time.
Sushma_HR: So, this is a brief summary about the project management. It's a 6 months of internship program, Monday to Saturday, working year, it's, like, it's Monday to Saturday, 30 hours, so minimum 30 hours of commitment of, internship. So, do you have any doubts or concerns?
Sushma_HR: You can, ask now.
Sushma_HR: And whoever turned off your video, could you please turn on your video?
Haniah fatim: I just had a doubt. Is the timings fixed, what you have said, or is there, like, a flexible timing, but 30 hours minimum per day?
Haniah fatim: Is that what I was on?
Sushma_HR: It's…
Haniah fatim: Okay.
Haniah fatim: Understand.
Chikamnene Vivian: Okay, my question is, you know I am on a different time zone with you people, like 1PM, Indian time is, 10.30AM in Nigerian time.
Chikamnene Vivian: So, since this is 30 hours per… 30 hours per week, do I… is it flexible? Do I work on my own time, or I will stick to Indian time?
Chikamnene Vivian: Because most times, the engine's working time might be Nigeria's sleeping time. That's why.
Sushma_HR: It's India timings only.
Sushma_HR: Because, everyone are working from 5pm to 9pm, so everyone are expected to work in that time.
Sushma_HR: So.
Sushma_HR: Any more doubts?
Chikamnene Vivian: I don't understand, can you repeat?
Sushma_HR: You… you're not audible, your voice is breaking.
Sushma_HR: It's great for me or for everyone, I don't.
Shivaansh: What time zone do you follow?
Shivaansh: Hello.
Sushma_HR: Okay.
Sushma_HR: So, let's go to the breakout room.
Sushma_HR: Sandy and Shivansh. Guys, just give us,
Sushma_HR: 3 to 5 minutes. We will be back with the result.
Sushma_HR: See, we are working in India time zones only.
Sushma_HR: We are not going to do any flexible to anything, because
Sushma_HR: most of our discussions, everything will be going in our time zone, 5PM to 9PM, and all are from
Sushma_HR: Oh.
Sushma_HR: In the end, like, all are following the same time zone, so we don't have different time zones or different time slots working.
Sushma_HR: Because it's a collaboration work, you need to collaborate with the teams, and you need to collaborate with the meetings. So, like, it's not, like, only the backend work, it's print, and also you need to be worked through discussions, etc.
Sushma_HR: Okay, I hope I answered to your question.
Sushma_HR: Can you tell.
Chikamnene Vivian: Exactly.
Sushma_HR: Okay, thank you.
Sujal Yadav: Is it over?
Haniah fatim: They told me to wait for a couple minutes, so that they'll announce the results.
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, the interview is still not over, we'll be back in some time.
Shivaansh: Oh… Guys, can you please turn on your cameras?
Shivaansh: Alright. So,
Shivaansh: Vivian and Rishabh, thank you so much for joining, but we will not be moving forward with you guys. You can leave.
Shivaansh: Guys, am I audible?
Sushma_HR: Yes, yes, you're audible.
Shivaansh: Vivian?
Sushma_HR: Rishi and Vivan, we appreciate your time and interest.
Sushma_HR: But, as of now, we are not forward with the next step. You both of you can leave the meet, and you can keep an eye for future opportunities.
Sushma_HR: Oh.
Sushma_HR: Okay. Sirisha, you can leave the mic, thank you. Guys, 4 of you, yeah.
Sushma_HR: Just give a minute.
Sushma_HR: Alright. See, now I will react to you, one by one, sharing your motivation to do this internship, why I4G, and why project management.
Sushma_HR: Three questions.
Sushma_HR: The first one… Your motivation to do this internship?
Sushma_HR: Why A4G, and why project management?
Sushma_HR: And also your career goals, sorry.
Sushma_HR: The four things.
Haniah fatim: Would you like me to start, or I can wait?
Sushma_HR: Yeah, good.
Shivaansh: Groshaws.
Haniah fatim: Okay, okay, so my name is Hania Fatima. I'll just give a sum up of all the four questions in one go, if that is okay.
Haniah fatim: So, coming to… I'm a computer science graduate from engineering, and from start, I've always been interested in project management, vice versa, and I've been inclined towards it from the start. I've been taking a few of these project management courses as well, and I have enrolled myself in
Haniah fatim: Correspondence Online MBA. That is on Saturdays, Sundays. There are 2 hours class on Saturdays, Sundays. So, that is what I'm doing to learn on the side as well.
Haniah fatim: And, the main motivation why I wanted to join this was,
Haniah fatim: I basically did an internship last year when I was in my college. It was a product-based internship. It was non-technical as well, from before also. And so, I realized that, I saw it, and I realized that since it was non-technical, I have experience in it as well. And since AI is also my background.
Haniah fatim: And since, A4G is, like, AI for good, and, so that is what I thought, that this aligns perfectly with what I want. So that is another biggest reason why I wanted to join, A4G and everything.
Haniah fatim: And
Haniah fatim: What, if you can tell me what other.
Sushma_HR: Hi, project management.
Sushma_HR: Okay, we are going by project management.
Haniah fatim: Okay, so it… like I told you, my career goal at the end of the day is to become a project manager at a higher level, at a… So that is what I… and then I saw that, see, this is an internship of 6 months, and that will give me so much of experience, so much of knowledge, so much of…
Haniah fatim: everything, and then maybe I can use whatever I've learned and then take it further into my career. Because what I realized as a project manager, you cannot directly, as a fresher, go into that position. You need experience. So, I thought that this would be a very good platform, because when you start as a fresher, you will be given so much opportunity to learn and see actually how everything works. So, I thought that this aligns perfectly.
Haniah fatim: And like I said, A4G, why A4G is because I have a computer science background, and since I've already studied AI, and I have done a startup internship at a startup company, which was a product-based company, which is a non-technical, where I handled, basically, promoting, marketing, social media campaigns, I have seen how to get the product across. And then what I saw… and then I have even
Haniah fatim: I really like the social awareness part of it, and then I even have an idea in my mind regarding the mental well-being aspect, which I was developing in my college time as well. So I thought that
Haniah fatim: maybe I can take that, and then maybe see, and then see how it goes. The idea which I have planned, I already have a plan in my mind, so I thought that this could contribute to the A4G, the mental well-beingness part.
Haniah fatim: So, that is all, I think, the 4 reasons.
Haniah fatim: The full answers to your question.
Sushma_HR: What exactly motivates you to choose your career in project management?
Haniah fatim: What motivates… okay, so, from the start…
Haniah fatim: Ahhh… In project manage… see, I think I'm,
Haniah fatim: I'm a people's person, I like to work in teams, I like to manage things, and I have always wanted to become an event manager from the start, I don't know why, if it is later or not.
Haniah fatim: And then, since I have a technical background as well, so regarding my exact interest with event management, project management, and my education, I thought that this is exactly what I want.
Haniah fatim: And then what I can take forward. So this is, I think a very good reason why I thought that… why I wanted to do project management from the start, like, after my 12th.
Haniah fatim: So…
Sushma_HR: Alright, thanks. Next.
Sujal Yadav: okay I choose project management because I enjoy bringing structure to work and making sure things actually get done in the planned way I like working with the different people organ organizing tasks and solving problems that come during my execution project management allow me to combine communication planning and problem solving in the role one role it gives me the opportunity to work on the different kinds of projects
Sujal Yadav: The tangible results from my efforts as I have completed my graduation.
Sujal Yadav: In the field of business, Management, so managing things is a one more option on my part.
Sujal Yadav: And from my previous internship, which was actually an IT field startup, so I managed their projects and marketing.
Sujal Yadav: around with the sales, so I interacted with the following clients and delivered their projects on time, and also.
Sujal Yadav: Insisting my team that how we should work on the next project.
Sujal Yadav: What motivates me? I'm motivated by this role, where I can bring a structure to work and see things move from planning to executing. I enjoy organizing tasks, solving small problems before they become big issues, and making sure work stays on track.
Sujal Yadav: The internships give me a chance to develop real project management skill in a practical environment while contributing to a meaningful work.
Sujal Yadav: And why A4G? I want to join A4G because it focus on AI for social goods, especially in the areas like sustainability, mental health, and responsible AI. Like that, the organization is not just building technologies.
Sujal Yadav: But also.
Sujal Yadav: thinking about the impact on the society. Working in such a mission-driven environment would allow me to contribute meaningful projects
Sujal Yadav: While learning how large multi-stakeholder initiatives are managed.
Sujal Yadav: And my long term career goals in project management is to grow strong into a strong project management profession who can handle complex.
Sujal Yadav: cross-functional project in the long term. I want to manage large initiatives where I can lead, plan, execute, and deliver across the team. Right now, I want to build a strong foundation in the coordination, risk management, and execution discipline, and gradually grow into the roles where I can take the ownership of the project.
Sushma_HR: Okay, alright. Next. Thank you.
Vidushi Sinha: Yeah, so, like, I am also a BTEC graduate, like, in computer science, and after that, like, I joined a company as an SD, and I worked there for 2 years.
Vidushi Sinha: So, in that working… while working in that company, like, they don't have real product managers or anything like that, because that is a startup company.
Vidushi Sinha: So, like, we have to do all the tasks, like, just for researching also for a particular product, or doing coding. So in that process, like, I learned that I am more aligned to this part of job, like, researching or managing projects, or like that.
Vidushi Sinha: So, at that point of time, I think of converting my career from, like, coder to the management side, so that's why I'm doing MBA also. And why A4G? So, basically, the main motive which I am impressed by is this, like, they are not.
Sushma_HR: Probably not.
Vidushi Sinha: planning to remove human for AI, like, rather than they are using AI for the human wellness. So that's the main thing, like, I'm attracted to the A4G concept.
Vidushi Sinha: And so, project management's also, like, I feel myself more aligned, and mainly my career goal…
Sushma_HR: Well…
Vidushi Sinha: Like, includes, basically, two.
Sushma_HR: That's appropriate.
Vidushi Sinha: In long term, like, I aspire to become a project manager and eventually move into strategic leadership roles also, like, where I can lead large-scale projects and, like, create basic business values and social impact combined. So that's the main… main…
Vidushi Sinha: focus of mine in the few, like, five to six years, so I also want to, like, continue learning or emerging technologies also, like, AI is the, like, today's the world of AI also.
Vidushi Sinha: So, the concept of this company and my future goals, so this completely aligned perfectly with me as of now.
Sushma_HR: Okay, being a coder, what exactly,
Sushma_HR: Motivates you to shift your career to the managed.
Vidushi Sinha: Yeah, because, like, that I said, like, there's a no product manager, in that startup. So, like, we as a coder only have to research, do researching and, documentation and, like, designing MVPs, all the things, for the role. So, like, I…
Vidushi Sinha: during that two years, I generally feel from my side, like, I am more aligned to that part, like, being a coder, I don't… I don't enjoy that part, but being… doing researching and planning, that's enjoyed myself more for doing work, and I…
Vidushi Sinha: Like, I feel motivated in doing that. It'll rather be, like, sitting behind the computer and doing coding all the day.
Shivaansh: Okay, so, we… does anyone else want to add anything?
Yashika: I'm left. I have to answer. So why project management? I also come from a developer experience background. And apart from the technical side and the coding side, I was always interested to know the why behind the product.
Yashika: to know the complete life cycle behind how the product is developed and how the research is done, how the documentation is done, how the prioritization is done. So I was inclined towards that. So that's why this shift from development to project management. So this internship will definitely add an experience to my career.
Yashika: So that's why I'm excited about this internship. And why 4G? Because as it is like using AI for like building the solutions and not losing human value to it, instead of we are leveraging AI to build sustainable solutions and for social economic issues and mental well-being.
Yashika: So that's an interesting part about it. So I want to be a part of this team and know how exactly the solutions are built and how AI is being leveraged.
Yashika: And my long-term goal is to get into a higher, project manager role, or a product or program manager role. So, this will be, like a baby step.
Yashika: to get into those kind of roles. And definitely, I'm very excited about learning from the team and knowing how the team works and everything.
Yashika: Thank you.
Shivaansh: Alright, does anyone else wanna add anything?
Shivaansh: Okay, guys, can you just give us 5 minutes? We'll get back to you.
Shivaansh: Sandy, can you join the breakout room?
Sandli Javadekar: Oh, yeah.
Shivaansh: Alright, hi guys, can you please turn on your cameras real quick?
Shivaansh: Okay, so from this round, Vidushi, thank you so much for joining, but for this round, we'll not be moving forward with you. You can keep an eye out for other opportunities as well. Thank you so much for joining. You can leave.
Shivaansh: moving forward this round, guys, we'll be moving for… we'll be moving you guys into breakout rooms, and taking individual questions for each one of you. Alright? So… yeah. I'll just assign rooms to you guys.
Shivaansh: Yep.
Shivaansh: Alright. Hi. Hi, Hanya, how are you? Am I pronouncing it right?
Haniah fatim: Yes, it's Hania, actually. Oh, by mistake, I don't think I wrote an A at the end for Fatima, so… my bad.
Shivaansh: My name is Shivansh Ramakrishnan Achar at Omisha Foundation, A4G. So.
Shivaansh: I'll be taking your HR on for now, alright?
Haniah fatim: Absolutely.
Shivaansh: a few questions for you. What are your career aspirations?
Shivaansh: And what… do they align with this internship? How do they align with this internship? And with our organization?
Haniah fatim: Okay.
Haniah fatim: So, can I go a bit on the backstory of how I wanted to do it? Like, so…
Shivaansh: Yeah, yeah, of course.
Haniah fatim: Yes. So, from 11th and 12th and all of my 10th, I think I'm a very social person. I love to speak with people. I think I'm a person who loves, who works well in teams.
Haniah fatim: And, yes, so I have taken up various, leadership opportunities. So, I've been a CR in my college for 3-4 years, and my 11th and 12th also, I was a student leader over there. So, from the start, and then I've taken part in various debate competitions and various mock parliaments or something, which shows my love for speaking, which shows my love for event manage… and then, what I saw was that product management, or project management.
Haniah fatim: two major criterias, which I was always very much interested in. Because at the end of the day, I wanted to become a project manager at a very good company. And what I realized is that when I went into it, because in my engineering all through my life, I didn't know that, like, coding, I do code, but I didn't find the passion.
Haniah fatim: So, that was… that is why I realized that maybe that is… I want to shift to MV as well. But I also want to start my career.
Haniah fatim: So, what I took was, I started with my online MBA from NMIMS University. It's gonna start from July 10th, and what I realized is that there are weekends, which is on Saturdays and Sundays in
Haniah fatim: in a flexible time, whenever you have time, you can get that part of that done. And, so that is what my initial part was. And then what I realized that I am taking a small course to understand about AI, about what is product, project management, as such. So that is what is my career goals. And how does it align
Haniah fatim: Well, with this organization, is that,
Haniah fatim: First of all, like I said, A4G, AI for good. I already have a background in computer science, AI, and what I found is that I can take
Haniah fatim: what I have as a technical background and my passion, and then bring it all together, all at once. And I really like… I went through your page, I went through all the things you've done, and and one more thing was that the mental well-being part really stood out to me, was that I actually, in my college, I did a project
Haniah fatim: Where we developed an app.
Haniah fatim: And there's an idea as well, in my mind, regarding how I… we can, cater to the mental well-being of students, of people who are working in companies. There's an idea in my mind, which is create… I created MindEase. If I… if you would like, I can actually share you the case study I've done.
Haniah fatim: So that is what I saw, and then when I saw it, I was like, oh, this aligns perfectly. So that is the biggest reason why I wanted to join this as well.
Shivaansh: All right. What is your motivation to do this internship?
Haniah fatim: my motivation to do this internship is that, like I said.
Haniah fatim: My main aim is to learn.
Haniah fatim: That is what is my major goal. Like, the stipend is just an addition which I'm getting. So, that is not the major goal. So, my major goal is to learn, to collaborate with people, and maybe gain the knowledge, so that in the future, when I'm eligible to sit at a bigger position, people can look at it and be like, okay, this girl has experience. So, and this is a 6-month internship, and I feel like this will give me a lot of
Haniah fatim: knowledge, because I feel like as an intern, you don't…
Haniah fatim: you have to, like, pick on, like, small, small things from different, different sides, and then you have to do different, different responsibilities. So I think that is what is, like, my major motivation, learning new things.
Shivaansh: Alright. Apart from that,
Shivaansh: Are you sure… what's your college timings?
Haniah fatim: Oh, I'm done with my college. I have graduated.
Haniah fatim: Are you looking for…
Shivaansh: Any thoughts?
Haniah fatim: Like I said, I want… I just started… I want… I realized that my goal is project management. I want to be a project manager.
Haniah fatim: So, I realized that from the start. Usually what happens is, they usually… people go technical background, and once they're in their 30s or something, they go into product or project management. But I wanted to… I knew from the start that I wanted to do that. So, I'm taking the time out to do courses, to time out, and then build my resume in a way
Haniah fatim: I can go that path.
Shivaansh: Alright, so you're not looking for any jobs right now, and you're looking for an internship, right?
Haniah fatim: Yes, knowledge and experience, basically.
Shivaansh: Apart from that, can you tell me…
Shivaansh: Do you have any other internships in the pipeline, any officer internships?
Haniah fatim: As of now, no, but I was looking to actively apply, so there was a course which I was doing.
Haniah fatim: gonna be very frank, Elevate IQ University. So, yes, so basically what it is, is that it provides me with 2 months of learning.
Haniah fatim: And then after that, there's a 2-month of project, which I have to do, and it is a project I do by myself in my free time, in the mornings. Not now, I'm still in the learning process. It can happen after September.
Haniah fatim: So, that part is there.
Haniah fatim: Gonna be very…
Shivaansh: We have, strict timings about 5 to 9 that we need you available.
Shivaansh: So, will you be able to commit?
Shivaansh: I think, yes.
Haniah fatim: 5 to 9 is a good time I can come in. On Saturdays as well?
Shivaansh: on Saturdays, we have Monday to Saturday working, 5 to 9, and you have… you'll be able to apply for leaves.
Shivaansh: Four days, or four leaves a month.
Shivaansh: And, we only give leaves on national holidays, so that's just your Independence Day and Republic Day.
Shivaansh: Oh, nice.
Haniah fatim: So basically, if I start, it won't even come in there.
Shivaansh: Yeah, not really. August 15th will come if you do.
Haniah fatim: Oh yeah, Independence Day, I really forgot about that.
Shivaansh: Okay, so what are your expectations from this internship?
Haniah fatim: My expectations from this internship is that, of course, learning, is what I've said, and then I want to get a good amount of work where I can actually learn and do it, and maybe in the future, like, have a team of my own, and then see…
Haniah fatim: Yep.
Shivaansh: Alright,
Shivaansh: You have done internships before this, right? I have done, yeah. So, what was your last round stipend?
Haniah fatim: My last one's stipend was $21,200.
Shivaansh: Good.
Shivaansh: Do you understand the stipend structure that is provided by this organization?
Haniah fatim: I did. I did. For the first two months, it says something around 5K, and then… so yes, that is again… see, again, again, this… the money criteria did hesitate to… out to me a bit, because it is very less as compared to what I was getting.
Shivaansh: Right.
Haniah fatim: Yes, so…
Shivaansh: So, we have a stable structure of 5…
Geetha: Good aftern.
Shivaansh: Yeah, sorry.
Geetha: Yeah, thank you. So, I cannot turn on my video. If I turn on my video, you cannot hear me. So, I'm facing some, like, you know, the signal issues. So, Hanya, it's, like, one straightforward question to you. So, you already completed your graduation.
Geetha: And you've done good internships with good staff,
Haniah fatim: Stand up.
Geetha: Why, again, you would like to do the internship, why not a full-time role, with a good pay?
Haniah fatim: Let me, clear that up.
Haniah fatim: For you, I would… initially would have loved to take up a full-time role, and I would… I'm still looking forward to a full-time role, but I have certain limitation, and that is being remote.
Haniah fatim: So, I don't know where I'll end up in a year or two. So, the location part is something which is…
Haniah fatim: Is it a bit of a difficulty to meet? So…
Geetha: I'm.
Haniah fatim: Looking for remote.
Haniah fatim: Full-time, I would love to, if there's a remote option.
Haniah fatim: But, like, right now… Yes.
Geetha: Are you not applying, remote full-time opportunities? Do you have any interviews or offers in pipeline, or in lined up, any interviews?
Haniah fatim: That's the thing, right? So, I realized that what my passion is, project management, product management, I've realized that I want to do. So, I realized that initially, it will be a lot of road bumps, it'll be a lot of difficulties getting to there, but see, many people for product management, my brother as well, he got into a role.
Haniah fatim: 30.
Haniah fatim: And I'm 20… I'm gonna turn 22. So, I want to skip that big…
Haniah fatim: age, and then I want to get into it as quickly as possible. So, for that, I need experience. So, in order for that.
Haniah fatim: I might have to do these small things, and then maybe once I build up my resume very well, I can apply for full-time opportunities with a better pay, with a better…
Haniah fatim: That is what I'm…
Geetha: Okay.
Geetha: Could you please let us know…
Haniah fatim: And, for increase in the stipend, is there any flexibility in that, or is it, like, fixed, fixed?
Shivaansh: So, no, that is a fixed stipend structure that we have. It's 5,000 for the first two months. That too, if we're able to commit 30 hours a week.
Shivaansh: That is a compulsory. On that basis, the stipend is calculated. Then for the next two months, you are appraised. Based on your appraisal, it increases to 7.5. And after the two months of 7.5, you'll have another cycle of appraisal that appraises to 10,000.
Haniah fatim: So, 30 hours is, like, measured.
Shivaansh: Yo.
Haniah fatim: So, if it's, like, 25 hours, so what… what happens with that?
Shivaansh: The stipend, the drawn stipend, will be cut accordingly to that.
Shivaansh: So, 30 hours a week adds up to 120 hours a month. 120 hours a month is something that we look forward to. If you do 118 hours, then the amount for that 2 hours will be cut.
Shivaansh: We have a… we have a structure of calculating the stipend.
Haniah fatim: So this is… there's a lot of time commitment to the… Definitely.
Shivaansh: Yeah, definitely.
Haniah fatim: Yes, I see.
Shivaansh: Sushma, you're not audible
Shivaansh: Alright, I just have a few more questions. I'll take your natural fit and outfit.
Shivaansh: I want you to keep the questions, answers short and crisp.
Shivaansh: Okay.
Haniah fatim: No worries.
Shivaansh: Yeah. Just give me a second before that.
Shivaansh: Alright, so my first question is, when you take up a new project, what do you try to understand when the task is assigned to you?
Haniah fatim: I think every task assigned has a problem statement attached to it, so I think as a product management or project management, the first role is to at first basically understand what the problem is, and try to understand, who the pers… who it is addressed to.
Haniah fatim: understand why the problem is coming up, and try… and try to, like, gather as much information about it as possible. That's the first thing I would do.
Shivaansh: Alright.
Shivaansh: Oh.
Shivaansh: Sometimes projects look fine on the surface, but feel risky. What kind of things make you uneasy even when nothing has gone wrong yet?
Haniah fatim: I think problems which, for example, issues… for example, if you take a medical part. So, if there's even a bit of a faulty diagnosis, there's a large amount of risk involved with it. So, I think issues which have a large amount of risk involved with it, that is what
Haniah fatim: we feel uneasy before stepping in, because if you have an AI program that says that the diagnosis is yes or no, it looks good from the start, but the level of… if the level of risk is high, then I think that is where the part of uneasiness comes in, and that is where we have to take prevention steps, I think.
Shivaansh: Alright, when someone senior or important asks for urgent work, what do you think through before agreeing?
Haniah fatim: So basically, if a senior or somebody answers, you naturally know that they're at a position higher to you, so you realize that you have to understand and give them importance, and then try to address the issue. But again, I would say that,
Haniah fatim: like, if it is something very… if you're stuck in a very, very, very important situation, and you cannot get out of it, I think the best way is to always be open to communication, and then tell them that you're in a bit of a difficulty, or a bit of a time…
Haniah fatim: pro… issue, then maybe they might understand, or if the problem is less, maybe you can take a bit of your time and then try to get it done, or maybe take help of your teammates or something and make sure that part is done. And then you…
Haniah fatim: Somehow get it done by using other people's help.
Shivaansh: Alright. How do people usually know that something is fully done when you're involved in a project?
Haniah fatim: I think, usually, the last part is the feedback part. So, when you're fully done is when you, for example, you send your product for testing, and then the results and the reviews and the feedback which you get.
Haniah fatim: If it is positive, and if it is according to your mark, then you can realize that, okay, I think we are satisfied with this product. If there's a certain threshold it crosses, then we can actually say that, okay, we can move forward.
Shivaansh: All right.
Shivaansh: Describe a decision you had to make quickly without having all the information.
Haniah fatim: Okay, you mean I have to answer in a product-related way, a project-related way?
Shivaansh: Yeah.
Haniah fatim: I see. Okay, so basically, there was a startup which I was working on, Rohirent.
Haniah fatim: So, what we realized was,
Haniah fatim: Initially, we did not have much of information on social media, how… whether it will work, whether it will not work, or… what happened was, we realized that we thought of taking an influencer, but we did not know
Haniah fatim: which demographic exactly is more… it's actually a UAE startup-based company, so we didn't know what demographic are we actually targeting to. So, what we realized is we didn't have much of information, because it was just a starting point. So, we found that there are so many Malayalis here, let us get a Malayali influencer and try to, you know.
Haniah fatim: promote. And then, luckily, to our luck, it actually worked out very well. It got a lot of engagement to us. So, we didn't have much information, but we just went with it, and then I think
Haniah fatim: We got it.
Shivaansh: Alright.
Shivaansh: Okay, just a few more questions.
Haniah fatim: No worries.
Shivaansh: Okay, so I'll take your organizational fit round now.
Shivaansh: When something you're involved in fails, what's the first question you ask yourself?
Haniah fatim: Feels what?
Shivaansh: When something you're involved in fails.
Shivaansh: What's the first question you ask yourself?
Haniah fatim: I'm sorry, I might have not got the question correctly. You said that…
Shivaansh: The project field.
Haniah fatim: Bing!
Shivaansh: Yeah, it fails.
Haniah fatim: I couldn't hear the word properly. I'm sorry.
Shivaansh: fails, what's the first question you ask yourself?
Haniah fatim: First question is, did we actually get it wrong from the start?
Haniah fatim: So, that is something… Just a second.
Haniah fatim: Okay, so that is the part where we discuss, like, did we actually get the problem correctly? So I think we have to, again, go back to the start and try to see, okay, is this the problem actually we're trying to solve? And then work our way from there. So that is where I would go back, to the starting point, to the board.
Shivaansh: Okay. What kind of behavior from others shut you down the fastest?
Haniah fatim: See, for me, I think… Shut me down the most.
Haniah fatim: Probably would be when they are not act.
Haniah fatim: For example, If they are… for me, I think it's the time.
Haniah fatim: For example, if not following a particular time, or not following a particular schedule, if they say a 9 o'clock meeting, and then… and they're at 10, and they say, oh, I forgot. I think that is what, like, shuts me down the most, or just gives me…
Haniah fatim: A not interested aspect.
Shivaansh: Alright, when something changes last minute, what's the first thing you do, mentally or practically?
Haniah fatim: when something changes last minute, I think the first thing you have to do is accept
Haniah fatim: we have to first accept it mentally. Okay, this is how something has been changed. So, you give yourself a few minutes, understand that, okay, this situation has happened.
Haniah fatim: understand it, validate it, and then, once that stress part is over, next you have to try focusing on the solution. This has happened, what is the next thing we do?
Haniah fatim: So that is what I would do.
Shivaansh: What do you instinctively tweak when you're given a task?
Haniah fatim: What do I tweak when I'm given a task?
Haniah fatim: What I personally believe is, you're given an end product.
Haniah fatim: There are multiple ways to reach it.
Haniah fatim: So, if there's a strict pathway to give, I would say that if it gets some… if there's any other way, if there's any other ethical way, more reasonable way which you can get faster, I would probably tweak the process and how it's done.
Shivaansh: When you mess up, who's the first person you usually tell?
Shivaansh: In an organization base.
Haniah fatim: Thank you for clarifying that. In an organization base, probably, I think you need to… I would do that with a colleague or somebody
Haniah fatim: a mentor.
Haniah fatim: Because somebody who is not exactly directly related to the project, maybe your colleague or your peer who's from another project, because you cannot go and directly tell that to the person. Maybe see, and then maybe try with them, try to have a talk with them, and then maybe they can understand you, and then maybe they can give you some tips, and then maybe you can actually go and then put forward your
Haniah fatim: Error in a more professional way to the person concerned.
Shivaansh: All right.
Shivaansh: Oh!
Shivaansh: Thank you so much. That's it from my side. Do you have any questions for us?
Haniah fatim: I'm good, thank you. Is there any… when will I get to know the results, how will.
Shivaansh: Yeah, so, I want you to drop your name, your number, and your email address, in the chat box.
Shivaansh: And if you'll be selected, we'll contact you in the next 2-3 days via WhatsApp. If you don't receive a message from us, you can consider that as a rejection from our side.
Haniah fatim: I understand, totally. So, can I switch off my camera and then, send.
Shivaansh: Drop your messages and drop your name, number, email, and you can leave.
Haniah fatim: Perfect. Thank you so much.
Shivaansh: Alright, thank you, thank you so much, you can leave.
Haniah fatim: Thank you so much.
Shivaansh: Sushma, okay, she also left.
Sandli Javadekar: No.
Shivaansh: My god.
Sandli Javadekar: Thank you.
Shivaansh: You will have integrity issues.
Sandli Javadekar: And main, like Shrishma said, you know, ki in the Google form, she was, you know, talking about incentives and stipend a lot, but now she was saying, you know, it's not, it's just an addition, so I think that's a bit, you know.
Shivaansh: That's what, that's what all the candidates do, honestly.
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, I just, you know, I just felt like in the way she was talking that she's not really valuing our organization, like…
Shivaansh: I'm just doing it because…
Sandli Javadekar: because he cannot find anything else.
Shivaansh: Yah.
Sandli Javadekar: That is the only bad thing that I not.
Shivaansh: From a psychology perspective, I found her pretty gullible.
Shivaansh: So I found, like, I thought, I think, like, if she starts working here, she will actively, I think she'll stop looking for job opportunities elsewhere.
Shivaansh: Because she'll get too involved with this, that's what I felt.
Sandli Javadekar: Once she puts her heart and soul in it, I think, yeah, then it'.
Shivaansh: Yeah, who do you wanna call next, Yashica or Sujan?
Sandli Javadekar: Let's call, social first.
Shivaansh: What are your expectations from soldier?
Shivaansh: Do we like it or do we not like it?
Sandli Javadekar: The thing is, his answers are very structured, but then I just thought that, you know, there was just this one thing. I felt like he was maybe chat GPT-ing a little bit, because they were too structured.
Shivaansh: I just want to see.
Sandli Javadekar: It's Postm.
Shivaansh: Get out, yeah.
Shivaansh: Alright, I'll take the HR round for this one.
Shivaansh: Do you wanna take the natural fit?
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, yeah, I have the questions ready also, if you saw, I've opened the thing in my lapt.
Shivaansh: That is if we move to the natural fitness.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, okay.
Shivaansh: Sushma, who is starting the work hub
Shivaansh: 10 minutes to the work up.
Shivaansh: Hello, Sushma.
Shivaansh: Anyways…
Sandli Javadekar: Also, I had a question, and even…
Sandli Javadekar: The National Fit Values, may you only ask one question from each category? One question from each category.
Shivaansh: In total, we asked 9 questions, 4 from NaturalFit, 5 from Oxford.
Shivaansh: Pardon?
Shivaansh: Hi, Sujal, how are you.
Sandli Javadekar: Oh yeah, I was noticing.
Sujal Yadav: I'm good, what about you guys?
Shivaansh: I'm good. Okay, Susan, tell me a bit about yourself. What do you do?
Sujal Yadav: Okay, so my name is Sujali Adava, I'm just graduated in 2025, and after my graduation from Bhuvaneshwar Target Academy of Technology
Sujal Yadav: come through an internship for business develop international business development executives from for that I use it it it is basically a startup in a Noida based company so it's basically to
Sujal Yadav: provide staffing to the foreign clients, and I manage… and on that way, they have also two or three more companies, so I also work as a marketing intern of one of their companies named HireFullStacks to manage their
Sujal Yadav: marketing roles, and through my previous internship, I managed the projects delivered
Sujal Yadav: To the clients, the software they are asking, initiating the process of all end-to-end process, so that's all from my side.
Sandli Javadekar: Are you still doing your internship?
Sujal Yadav: No, it's over, last month.
Sandli Javadekar: It was a marketing internship.
Sujal Yadav: Actually, it's for the International Business Development internship. Basically, the company is in startups, so it runs two or three companies. So, for the Expolo, I act as a Business Development Executive. For HireFullstack, I'm working as a Marketing Intern, and in Expolo, I'm also handling their operations, projects.
Sujal Yadav: So basically, it's a mess- mess-up task.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, and you are based in Move Nation?
Sujal Yadav: Not yet, I'm currently living in New Delhi.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: Just a minute.
Shivaansh: Okay, my bad, that was the other HR. Okay, what are your career aspirations? Also, I forgot to ask, so you said you just graduated, right?
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, in 2025, so…
Shivaansh: So, will you be able to come at 9 to 5?
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, I will.
Shivaansh: Sorry, 5 to 9, my bad. 5 to 9. 5 p.m.
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, yeah.
Shivaansh: abstract timings.
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, I heard, I heard it.
Shivaansh: You graduated, why are you not looking for full-time?
Sujal Yadav: Actually, I'm a fresher currently, so I'm not getting that much expected thing, and right now, I want to learn the…
Sujal Yadav: best expect for the future growth. So, I want to learn everything which is trending in the market right now.
Shivaansh: Do you have any, jobs or internships in pipeline?
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, actually, I have worked 2 or 3 project management internships in.
Shivaansh: No, no, have you applied elsewhere where you were waiting for the reply or something?
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, I have one internship, I have applied, and I'm waiting for it.
Sujal Yadav: But I don't guess it's aligned with my pipelines.
Shivaansh: Alright. What is your motivation to do this internship?
Sujal Yadav: My motivation is, basically, I want that roles that can… I can bring structure… structure to work and same thing, moving from planning to executions. I enjoy organizing tasks, solving problems.
Sujal Yadav: And making sure that work stays on track.
Sujal Yadav: Basically, I want to… I… from my recent internship, I also managed a couple of people, couple of projects from the foreign clients, so I'm getting the exposure that I can build a career in project management, rather than marketing sales and… or sales.
Shivaansh: Alright. Okay, what was your last one, Stipend?
Sujal Yadav: Actually, it was 15K.
Sujal Yadav: But it is on offer.
Sujal Yadav: It is all office.
Shivaansh: I'm aware of this type of structure in our organization.
Sujal Yadav: Currently, I have just gone through it, but…
Shivaansh: So, it's 5000 for the first 2 months.
Shivaansh: Well, that is, if you complete 30 hours a week.
Shivaansh: 30 hours a week is a mandate. And post that, you will have an appraisal. You have two appraisal cycles. In first appraisal cycle, if you get a rating of 4 and above, you're appraised to 7,500. And in the next cycle, if you're appraised 4 and above, you get an appraisal of 10,000.
Sujal Yadav: Okay.
Shivaansh: Are you okay with that stipend structure?
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, I'm quite okay, because at that early stage, I just don't want to focus on many things, I just want to focus on the things I can get from that internship.
Sujal Yadav: Money is a secondary thing for right now.
Shivaansh: All right. Works. Also, can I know a bit about your family background? Who are there in your family, and what do they do?
Sujal Yadav: Actually, I have a joint… semi-joint family, you can say. My grandfather owns a logistic business, my father has a restaurant in my home.
Sujal Yadav: And I have a younger brother who helps my father to manage… helps my father and grandfather to manage the business, and my mother is a housewife.
Shivaansh: All right.
Shivaansh: Okay. So, okay, we'll be moving forward with the natural fitment round. Sandy, do you want to take the natural fit round?
Sandli Javadekar: Oh, yeah.
Sujal Yadav: Let me see. Hold.
Sandli Javadekar: Hi Sujal, I'm Sandhi, so I'll be starting with your natural fit round.
Sujal Yadav: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: So, when you take up a new project, what do you try to understand clearly before you begin assigning or doing your…
Sandli Javadekar: Tasks.
Sujal Yadav: Sorry to interrupt, but your voice is a little familiar.
Sujal Yadav: You're not, audible.
Sandli Javadekar: When you take up a new project.
Sandli Javadekar: What do you try to understand clearly before you begin assigning or doing your tasks?
Sujal Yadav: So, first, I've set the requirements, what the expectation of the client, and how we're going to fulfill it, and also I've scheduled the tasks according to the pipeline, and what time we are able to deliver that things, and I'm ensuring it every small aspect
Sujal Yadav: Expect that it did not carry any bad, bad, vulnerable things, so it harms the project. So I always take end-to-end decisions to make the project work fluently and deliver through the time.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, tell me about a time, you warned others about a possible issue before it actually happened.
Sandli Javadekar: And what made you speak up about it?
Sujal Yadav: So, I take the responsibility, because I'm coordinating with my teams and projects.
Sandli Javadekar: Rather than…
Sujal Yadav: blaming other people for that works if the project assigned to me it's all responsibilities I have to take that responsibility.
Sandli Javadekar: No, I'm asking, tell me about a time where you have previously, you know, an incident has happened with you when you've warned others about a possible issue.
Sujal Yadav: Okay, so, I would like…
Sujal Yadav: Yeah, yeah, actually, I have. It was a foreign client, and we had to deliver the software through AWS, but currently, there's a lot of end-to-end server issues. We cannot deliver it in time.
Sujal Yadav: So, I take the meetings from the client and apologize about our things, but later on, after delivering the things, the client is quite happy, and it does not
Sujal Yadav: Have aptic our relations.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: Have you ever realized midway that a task you were working on wasn't adding much value?
Sandli Javadekar: And what did you do then?
Sujal Yadav: So, one of my incident that I have to deliver person, not remotely, there was a project on US-based company, so they want a full-stack engineer, so I connected with two or three pressures, but
Sujal Yadav: at the minute of the task, the company doesn't like their way of thinking. So, on that way, I take the responsibilities, I change the
Sujal Yadav: overall structure, I change the candidates, and take… and give the best I can do for them, and end up…
Sujal Yadav: Doing the things great, rather than messing it up.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: What's harder for you, starting the tasks or finishing them, and how do you deal with that?
Sujal Yadav: Basically, starting a task is quite a bit harder, because starting
Sujal Yadav: Involves courageousness and all informations, but dealing is quite a good thing because you have structured manner of.
Sujal Yadav: All the things you have planned from the start.
Sujal Yadav: And delivering it on the right time is a good thing, rather than ending up.
Sujal Yadav: So, starting is…
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, have you ever questioned a rule, process, or instruction because it didn't make sense to you?
Sujal Yadav: For, yeah, for my experience, I haven't do that kind of things in my previous company.
Sujal Yadav: Because I joined as a intern, so…
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sujal Yadav: My responsibility to take the things as, take the knowledge, take the responsibilities as far as possible from my side.
Sandli Javadekar: Shivansh, would you like to take that organizational fit interview, or should I go ahead with that as well?
Shivaansh: You can go ahead with that as well, if you wanna.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: So…
Shivaansh: Do you want me to take it?
Sandli Javadekar: I need to… To your insurance.
Shivaansh: You take this one.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay,
Sandli Javadekar: Sujal, okay, so tell me, when something you're involved in fails, what's the first question you ask yourself?
Sujal Yadav: If I failed on something, the first question I ask was, what things I have done?
Sujal Yadav: That lead to the failure, I question myself rather than.
Sujal Yadav: Questioning other people, I figure out what the things I have done before the things failed.
Sujal Yadav: Rather than blaming or taking disappointments and take a lessons to what should I do next that this kind of situation won't happen.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: What kind of behavior from others shuts, like, shuts you down the fastest?
Sujal Yadav: I guess not responding from a multiple times.
Sujal Yadav: Just you are asking something, you don't have that knowledge, but the person is acting like he is a main character.
Sujal Yadav: people, and he just ignores your things. That shuts me, I guess. It's not a good behavior in an organization.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, how do you usually realize that your approach is not working?
Sujal Yadav: After 2 or 3 attempts.
Sujal Yadav: I do as as best I can do for them, but if they are not responding the way I want it, I simply.
Sujal Yadav: Shuts off the, shuts off the things and connections, con-conversations.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: Mmhm.
Sandli Javadekar: What's an idea you had that didn't work originally, but you'd still like to… Try it again differently.
Sujal Yadav: You are just… your name is clicked, so… You can repeat the question.
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, can you hear me now?
Sujal Yadav: Yah.
Sandli Javadekar: What's an idea that you had earlier, but it did not work?
Sandli Javadekar: But you would like to still try that idea again differently.
Sujal Yadav: So, basically, when I'm in my college, I want to run a startup. I had a business… I had an idea.
Sujal Yadav: That we serve the foreign clients.
Sujal Yadav: Before that, before AI was new to the market.
Sujal Yadav: So, we and our team are discussing about how we can implement or just create web pages
Sujal Yadav: To other small businesses.
Sujal Yadav: But initially, we don't have that kind of people, because in colleges, people are much distracted, rather than focusing on building something. So that's the thing I regret.
Sujal Yadav: I killed, you can see.
Sujal Yadav: We're connecting to the right people.
Sandli Javadekar: Oh.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: I'll ask you the last question, what kind of praise makes you uncomfortable?
Sujal Yadav: That rude behaviour and blaming the things I, I haven't.
Sujal Yadav: Do anything about that.
Sandli Javadekar: No, I'm asking what kind of praise makes you uncomfortable.
Sujal Yadav: Praise… I did not understand the crux of the word, praise.
Sujal Yadav: Can you a little elaborate it?
Sandli Javadekar: You know, like when someone praises you for the work you've done.
Sujal Yadav: Okay, so, kind of, it's basically motivation, motivating you, I guess. So, I like, I don't like the things that.
Sujal Yadav: Monetary terms, basically, what value it will add to my career.
Sujal Yadav: In, in the terms of motivation.
Sandli Javadekar: Please.
Sujal Yadav: Many candidates prefer monetary terms praise, but rather than preferring monetary, I basically focus on the skill sets.
Sujal Yadav: What new thing I wanna take from that?
Sujal Yadav: per people.
Sujal Yadav: How they praise my work after seeing the praise after seeing my work.
Sujal Yadav: So, it's, it's a good thing from my side that people are praised, I, I get the attention of that people that I have get praised from score something.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, that's it from my end.
Sandli Javadekar: Shivansh, you can continue.
Shivaansh: Alright, thank you so much, Sujal, for joining. Just drop your name, your number, and your email ID in the chat box, and we'll reach out to you in the next 2-3 days, if you're selected. We'll reach out through WhatsApp. If you don't get a reply from us in the next 2-3 days.
Shivaansh: You can consider that as a rejection from our side.
Sujal Yadav: Okay, and I just wanted to ask what the things I can change after you have heard the interview of, I guess, 2 hours. So, what's the one thing you didn't like in my interview, or the thing…
Shivaansh: One thing, Sujal, that we felt was that you were reading a lot of questions, the answers, at least during the outfit, so maybe you can change that a bit, come a bit prepared for that. Other than that.
Shivaansh: I have no… nothing from my side. Sandy, do you have anything?
Sandli Javadekar: No, maybe just, you know, prepare in advance, be clear about, you know, what you're going to say in the interview, so…
Sujal Yadav: Actually, I would like to add something. So, I'm not reading, I just prepared the notes on my…
Sujal Yadav: things that… that's the thing. Thank you for the feedback, guys. Appreciate it.
Shivaansh: Alright, thank you so much.
Sujal Yadav: You have to state that number, email ID, and what else?
Shivaansh: Name, your number, your email ID.
Sujal Yadav: Okay.
Sujal Yadav: Thank you, guys.
Shivaansh: Thank you.
Sandli Javadekar: Thank you.
Sujal Yadav: I have sent it, have a great day.
Shivaansh: You can leave now. Thank you.
Sujal Yadav: Thank you guys for having me, have a great day.
Shivaansh: Thank you.
Shivaansh: Okay, Sandy, what do you think about him?
Sandli Javadekar: He didn't understand the meaning of praise, only he's not getting, you know, the basic, genuine questions, so I was just very surprised by that.
Shivaansh: Okay, so we have one last candidate, Yashica.
Sandli Javadekar: Yes.
Sandli Javadekar: Also, Joe, the questions you asked in the HR round, did you have a different PDF for that? Because Sushma hasn't shared that.
Shivaansh: Yeah, it's, you would have received an updated shortlist candidate over there if you go.
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah.
Shivaansh: Caribbean as per India.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: Oh.
Shivaansh: Hi Yashica, how are you.
Sandli Javadekar: No.
Shivaansh: You're not audible.
Yashika: Hello, I'm not audible now.
Shivaansh: Yeah, your voice is very muffled, if you can talk a bit louder.
Yashika: Hello? Yeah, I'm on.
Shivaansh: Yeah, yeah.
Shivaansh: Alright. So, hi, Ashika. Tell me a bit about yourself. What do you do?
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Yashika: So I'm Yasha Kadiria, and I'm from Bod
Yashika: And I've done my B.Tech from the UCRC. And after that, I have around 3 years of experience as a diplomat.
Yashika: at Accenture, and now I'm pivoting my path into project management.
Sandli Javadekar: And whoops.
Yashika: We got a new guy.
Yashika: And now I'm involved, so I just need to understand what's going on.
Shivaansh: So you've graduated, right.
Sandli Javadekar: Yes.
Shivaansh: All right.
Shivaansh: So why are you looking for an internship, not for the job?
Yashika: So, as I'm from a developer, background, I wanted to, like, gain experience and learn from the basic steps.
Yashika: So, doing an internship will allow me to do so, and, like, planning part, how the execution part is done, how the documentation is done, interning with someone, and then learning from that.
Yashika: I feel that will be beneficial for me before taking it in a full-time role. So that's why that's that. That was my thinking.
Shivaansh: Alright, have you applied anywhere else for an internship? Do you have a pipeline offer?
Yashika: No, no, no, no offers currently.
Shivaansh: Alright. Okay, what is your motivation to do this internship?
Yashika: So my motivation to do this internship, as I said, like I'm from a developer background, so my motivation was always not to just do the work.
Yashika: But to know, the why behind the product, like, why we are building what we are building, and how the planning is done, how we are able to come to that solution. So, to know end-to-end life cycle of,
Yashika: a product, or a project, or a task. So, I wanted to get into that, like, how the, like, timelines are.
Shivaansh: Yeah. What's up? Hello! The sector, the main idea is shared. Right?
Yashika: I should ask.
Shivaansh: Big one.
Shivaansh: Yeah, sorry. Will you be available from 5 to 9?
Yashika: Yes, yes, I'll be available.
Yashika: Monday to Sat.
Shivaansh: Here.
Shivaansh: Just give me one second, alright?
Yashika: Sure.
Shivaansh: Tell me a bit more about your… about your family background. What… who all are there in your family, and what do they work in?
Yashika: Okay, so I live with my dad, and my mom had passed away in COVID, so… and I have two elder sisters, both of them are married, one lives in Mumbai and one lives in Indore, both of them are working.
Yashika: And yeah, and my dad is into property business.
Shivaansh: Okay.
Shivaansh: Okay, what are your expectations from this internship?
Yashika: My expectations from this internship is to, as I said, like, I wanted to know, like, how the research is done, and how to
Yashika: you know, work for the real world projects. As in a 4 G. We're using AI. So that is an add on like add on example, that how actual AI solutions are built and not to lose the human value, but to leverage AI into solutions, into mental wellbeing and sustainable sustainable solutions.
Yashika: And,
Yashika: also like how like, how to coordinate with the team cross cross team collaboration. And how the resources are being aligned, how the prioritization is done. And
Yashika: how to maintain the timeline, and also to also to check like the quality of the product is being delivered.
Yashika: and not to compromise on the deliver deliverables, and to how to like maintain the risk management, preventing the risk, and how to solve the issue before the issue arises. I want to like, get deep dive into it. So this internship will definitely be an add on
Yashika: For the… for my career, as well as a learning path.
Shivaansh: Alright, what was your last round stipend?
Yashika: So I was on, 5.5 LPA at Accenture.
Shivaansh: Okay. Do you understand this title structure over here?
Yashika: Yes, yes, I'm, I read about this type of instruction.
Shivaansh: Do you have any questions regarding that?
Yashika: No, like, it is fixed, right?
Shivaansh: Yeah.
Yashika: Okay.
Shivaansh: 5 for the first 2 months, based on the appraisal, 7.5 for the next 2, and 10 for the next 2.
Yashika: Yes, yes, I am aware about it.
Shivaansh: Alright. Alright. Sandy, can you take a natural fit round? I'll be back in 2 minutes. There's an issue with the workup meeting. I'll be back in 2 minutes, alright.
Sandli Javadekar: Hi, Yashica, how are you doing
Sandli Javadekar: Hi. My name is Sandhvi, I'll be doing your National Fit and Organizational Fit interview, okay?
Sandli Javadekar: Hello, Yashica, am I aud Thank you.
Sandli Javadekar: So… tell me about a time, when people on a project were confused, you know, about who was supposed to do what. Like, there was confusion among the tasks and, you know, the way tasks were given. And how did you notice this confusion, and, you know, what did you… what the steps… what all steps did you take to avoid this?
Sandli Javadekar: Later on.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, okay.
Yashika: So, I'll tell you an example from my last encounter.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Yashika: Oh.
Yashika: I wasn't.
Sandli Javadekar: It's going to.
Yashika: I'm really unhappy with that.
Yashika: Sorry, we had to…
Sandli Javadekar: Madam.
Sandli Javadekar: Times.
Yashika: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: Thank you.
Yashika: a proper KPI sheet and a task tracker. And then I assigned individual developers the proper task.
Yashika: Thank you.
Sandli Javadekar: And they need to be recorded.
Sandli Javadekar: proper signing was made.
Yashika: This will cause no uproot.
Sandli Javadekar: What is the, what is the day-to-day task and to finance the delivery?
Sandli Javadekar: Thank you.
Sandli Javadekar: Skip.
Yashika: So, the task, which is done, or.
Sandli Javadekar: So the tracking part was done by me. The planning part was already done, just task planners and everything.
Sandli Javadekar: Thank you, my cow. Yes, ma'am.
Sandli Javadekar: I'll be fat, fat, not to fat the people
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, and, you know, now when you're talking, can you just speak a bit slower? Because, you know, your voice is not coming that clear.
Yashika: Okay, so am I audible?
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, now you are, now it's okay, I'm just staying from the
Sandli Javadekar: I'll just speak to her a little loudly and clear, like, slowly.
Yashika: I don't.
Sandli Javadekar: Sometimes.
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, can you hear me?
Yashika: Yes, yes, you want to.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, sometimes, projects look fine on the surface, but they still feel risky. So what kind of things make you uneasy, even when nothing has gone wrong yet?
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, so… what makes me uneasy? First, like, what if…
Sandli Javadekar: Something gets stuck or there's a glitch that makes me like,
Sandli Javadekar: like a little bit of uneasiness. And, like, if… and second thing, if the issue arises, do we have the proper resource alignment to solve that issue? And, third, it's, like, have a proper mitigation plan, like, if this issue arises, proper solution, do we have that?
Yashika: So, to do that, like, like, there should be a proper risk register, or a risk manager, kind of, report to be made, like, it's just…
Sandli Javadekar: For sure, I usually have this kind of solution, and…
Yashika: That, like, in future, we don't have… we are not, like, planning for that, so those are the things, like, that will…
Sandli Javadekar: When someone senior or important asks for urgent work, what do you think before agreeing, and what factors, you know, matter most to you?
Yashika: Okay, so before agreeing, I'll just check what is the priority of the task given by that leader and what is the priority of my task which I'm working currently.
Yashika: Well, prioritize both of, I'll not say no, but I'll prioritize both of the tasks.
Yashika: Which is to be done at first, and then I'll communicate accordingly, like, this is my timeline, and this is the work that I'm doing, and how much time I'll take for this.
Sandli Javadekar: And accordingly, I'll have 5 pumps.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay. Many tasks, you know, get stuck at the final stage. From your experience, why does this happen, and what do you personally do to avoid this?
Yashika: Oh, fine.
Sandli Javadekar: Hello?
Yashika: Maybe, like,
Yashika: Individually, the people who are working on different tasks, and when everything is aligned, then, maybe
Yashika: To, like, individual solutions from work.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Yashika: That can be the issue at the end. Like, individually, the task…
Yashika: can be, like, like, are workable, but if we align them together, what if it does not work? What if something fails? What if, what if something.
Sandli Javadekar: That's… Okay. Describe a decision you had to make quickly, without having all the information.
Yashika: Like,
Sandli Javadekar: Thank you.
Yashika: But, like, I'm,
Sandli Javadekar: It's okay, you can just try to remember and then answer.
Yashika: So, like, in my past experience at Excelsior, like, I was a developer, I was not a developer there.
Yashika: So, we were, supposed to, like, work on the task that we did.
Yashika: There you go.
Sandli Javadekar: Like, once there was an issue placed by the tester.
Yashika: And, I had to inform them without, you know, consent.
Yashika: Without getting proper employment.
Sandli Javadekar: For my love.
Yashika: I responded according to my understanding, technical understanding.
Yashika: Oh.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Yashika: Whatever it was, I, I decided to send you them.
Sandli Javadekar: Oh my god, it'.
Yashika: It was not available at the time. And please urgently respond to the testing.
Sandli Javadekar: That, that's… Okay, now we…
Sandli Javadekar: Going forward with your organizational setup.
Sandli Javadekar: What's something people usually rely on you for?
Sandli Javadekar: We're learning for, A quick responder, but I'm the.
Yashika: people in the land for, like, I'll be available for them to listen to the issues, or to solve the issues, even if I don't know completely, but I'll listen to them.
Sandli Javadekar: I tried to understand, I tried to do my research.
Yashika: And then you can read them that. I feel like I'm, like, that book.
Sandli Javadekar: I know how to manage people and how to tackle this, how to collaborate with teams.
Sandli Javadekar: Who is the hardest type of person for you to work with?
Sandli Javadekar: There's a lot of people to work with, who are, not a good listener.
Sandli Javadekar: like, in a, in a team, you know, like, it's very, I feel it's very important to listen to other person, other person's perspective also, you know.
Yashika: They're not completely like.
Sandli Javadekar: But it's…
Yashika: I think it's very important to listen to them.
Sandli Javadekar: And correct them that this was the issue, or you can let, doctor, answer this.
Sandli Javadekar: So there are some people who just, who feel like,
Sandli Javadekar: I really like to do this.
Sandli Javadekar: listen to what other person is saying. So, at times, I've, faced that… those kind of…
Sandli Javadekar: And how do you usually handle working with them anyways?
Yashika: Yeah, I tried to, like, be patient with them, first of all, and then I went ready to write them.
Sandli Javadekar: I'll.
Yashika: Every time that you actually feel like even if I'm not right all the time but
Sandli Javadekar: Like, it's…
Yashika: It will be a good environment if we work together, if we listen to each other and try to
Yashika: Listen to everyone.
Sandli Javadekar: And what is like the return is also capable of giving good ideas.
Yashika: We don't need to have that good atmosphere.
Sandli Javadekar: I tried to communicate with my classmates very politely.
Yashika: Like, it depends on them, how their day is going to be.
Sandli Javadekar: How do you usually realize that your approach is not working?
Sandli Javadekar: My phone is not working, like, if the following… if I've assigned some tasks to, like, following more, like, people who are junior to me, and if they're not able to follow with the…
Sandli Javadekar: follow with my instructions or my guidelines, then I feel like I'm not able to.
Yashika: communicate properly, or I'm not able to, like, convey them the proper,
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, that's good. That's good.
Sandli Javadekar: There's a question here.
Sandli Javadekar: Nice.
Sandli Javadekar: You've joined what kind of problems, do you enjoy thinking about?
Sandli Javadekar: No, that's not what I'm saying.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: Actually, when I talk to users, and they're facing some.
Yashika: Thank you.
Sandli Javadekar: 19 pounds.
Sandli Javadekar: to actually, think about that problem, like, I was supposed to be in that place.
Sandli Javadekar: I know.
Sandli Javadekar: To, like, you know, like, 5, like, What?
Yashika: Can be the solution how to like.
Sandli Javadekar: No.
Sandli Javadekar: And, when you mess up, who's the first person you usually tell?
Sandli Javadekar: Like, mess up is not, like, okay.
Sandli Javadekar: Yeah, yeah, organization, obviously.
Yashika: So my reader, first of all, like, who am I reporting to?
Sandli Javadekar: Cheers.
Yashika: I guess that's important.
Sandli Javadekar: Please.
Yashika: They should, the correct person should know, like, this is the…
Sandli Javadekar: Yes,
Sandli Javadekar: I've, like, done something wrong, then I've messed up, and so I think those… maybe they can help me, and they can help me correct, and, not to, like, do that again.
Sandli Javadekar: I think, that person has come.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay, that's it from my end. Shalan, you can go ahead.
shivaansh: Alright. Thank you so much, Yashika, for joining. Can you just drop your, phone number, your name, and your email ID? And if you'll be selected, you'll get a message from us in the next 2 to 3 days. If not, you can consider that as a rejection.
Yashika: Okay, I'll drop my, name, phone number, and email ID in the chat.
shivaansh: Yes.
shivaansh: Alright, thank you. You can leave now.
Yashika: Yeah, thank you. Thank you for inviting me.
shivaansh: Thank you so much.
Sandli Javadekar: Thank you.
shivaansh: Alright.
shivaansh: What do you think?
Sandli Javadekar: I think she's okay,
Sandli Javadekar: I didn't see, you know, a very, you know, energetic… I didn't really feel like, you know, she was energetic or, you know, had that much passion or anything, but if we assign her tasks, she'll do it, but, you know, I didn't really feel like she'll have that, you know, internal motivation or enthusiasm or anything.
Sandli Javadekar: They're all Alright, join the work hub now. I'll also join in sometime.
shivaansh: All right.
Sandli Javadekar: Okay.
Sandli Javadekar: No. Goodbye.